Guide to the City and Regional Planning Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- State and International Planning, 1914-1990; Series II
  - Connecticut
    - Urban Renewal
      - Workable Program Of The City Of New Haven, 1957 April (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Water and Air Pollution
      - Air Pollution Control Code Of the City Of New Haven, 1969 January (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - A Water Pollution Abatement Program, Undated (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Zoning Ordinances
      - Building Zone Ordinance for the City Of New Haven, 1948 August (Box 16, Folder 13)
      - Market Reports for New Haven, 1962-1963, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 14)
      - New Haven Citizen Action Commission, Annual Reports, 1962-1963, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 15-17)
      - Proposed Regional Zoning Code For The New Haven Metropolitan Area, 1948 August (Box 16, Folder 18)
      - Redevelopment Plan for the Oak Street Redevelopment Area, 1962 May (Box 16, Folder 19)
      - Rezoning For New Haven, 1962 May (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Other States
    - Illinois
      - Chicago's World-Wide Influence In City Planning, 1914 July (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - The Geographic Background Of Chicago, 1926 October (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Missouri
      - History: Physical Growth Of The City Of St. Louis, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - St. Louis: A Fond Look Back, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - New York
      - Bronx
        - Bronx Plan: A Report On Physical Development Planning, 1969 August (Box 17, Folder 5)
        - Meanwhile In The South Bronx, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - Brooklyn
        - Analysis Of Decision Making In South Brooklyn, 1970 January (Box 17, Folder 7)
        - East Flatbush At The Threshold, 1968 Apt (Box 17, Folder 8)
        - Greenpoint Industrial Renewal Program, 1970 May (Box 17, Folder 9)
        - Model Cities, 1970 February (Box 17, Folder 10)
        - Prospect Park Alliance, Undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
      - Manhattan
        - Chelsea Action Planning Program, Undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
        - Lincoln Square Community Action Planning Program, Undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
      - Metropolitan Area
        - A Consultant's Report To The Tri-State Transportation Committee, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 14)
        - Measure Of A Region, 1967 May (Box 17, Folder 15)
        - Outline Of The Second Regional Plan, 1965 August (Box 17, Folder 16)
        - Regional Forecast, 1985, 1985 August (Box 17, Folder 17)
        - Study Area, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 18)
      - New York City
        - City Planning Commission, 1940 January (Box 17, Folder 19)
        - Construction Schedule For Arterial Highways And Parkways, 1946 June (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Texas
      - Austin Creeks, Undated (Box 17, Folder 21)
      - Dallas
        - Downtown Dallas Walkways Guide, Undated (Box 17, Folder 22)
        - The Kessler City Plan For Dallas, 1924 December-1925 January (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - International
    - Africa
      - An Autonomous Housing Prototype For Low Income Families, 1977 May (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Housing In Ghana, Undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - Housing And Town-Planning In Morocco, Undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Housing In Liberia, Undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Housing In Nigeria, Undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - Report on Town Planning In Nigeria, 1965 January (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - Urbanization In African Social Change, 1963 January (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Australia
      - Planning And Development Of Towns And Cities In South Australia, 1919 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Canada
      - Annual Report, Central Mortgage And Housing Corporation, 1971 March (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - Canada Housing Statistics, 1971 March (Box 18, Folder 10)
      - Housing In Canada, 1946-1970 (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - Montreal
        - Métropole Les Cahiers D'Urbanisme, 1964 April (Box 18, Folder 12)
        - Répertoire Des Noms De Rues, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 13)
        - Superficies Des Municipalité s, 1964-1969 (Box 18, Folder 14-15)
      - Toronto
        - Proposed Plan For Toronto, 1967 June (Box 18, Folder 16)
        - Proposals For A New Plan For Toronto, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - France
      - Preliminary Project of the United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization, 1953 April (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Great Britain (Box 18, Folder 19)
      - Lothians Regional Survey And Plan, Undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Oxford Preservation Trust Committee On Planning And Reconstruction (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Reading Our Architectural Heritage, Undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - A Report Of The City Architect And Director Of Housing On Speke, 1946 October (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Netherlands
      - The Dutch Hydraulics Laboratories: A Miniature World Of Water, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - Report On Physical Planning In The Netherlands, 1960 September (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - Rim-City Holland: Problems Of A Metropolis In The Making, 1958-1959 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - The Zuiderzee Works, 1948 January (Box 19, Folder 8)
- City Planning Subject Files, 1873-2000; Series III
  - Air Rights
    - Study of Air Rights, 1967 January (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - A Study Of Air Rights And Their Use In Los Angeles, 1966 February (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Study Of Terminal Transfer Facilities In Conjunction With Urban Freeways, 1967 June (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Area Economic Redevelopment
    - A Framework For The Analysis Of Depressed Areas, 1964 May (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Development and Planning Areas Of The United States, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Directory Of Approved Projects, 1966 September (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Eligible Areas and Maximum Grants-In-Aid, 1964 April (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Local Economic Programs: A Case Book, Undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Maximum Grant Rates For Public Works Grants in Qualified Areas, 1966 July (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Regional Development In Post-Industrial Society, 1964 May (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Regional Economic Development In The United States, Part 1, 1967 October (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Regional Economic Development In The United States, Part 2, 1967 October (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Summary List Of Redevelopment Areas, 1964 October (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Campus Plans-Inner City
    - A College Grows In The Inner-City, Undated (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Drexel Institute Of Technology, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1963 March (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Report Of The Committee Of Site Consultants, 1968 February (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Capital Improvement Planning And Budgeting
      - A Government-Wide Program Budget, 1967 February (Box 20, Folder 17)
      - Federal Budgeting, 1964 February (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Columbia Maryland
    - A Brand New City For Maryland (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Can These Thinkers Help Put Across A Vast New Town?, 1964 December (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Cities-The New Scale, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Columbia: A New Town For Howard County, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Columbia: City In The Country, 1964 March (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - The Columbia Newsletter, 1966-1968 (Box 20, Folder 23-29)
    - Presbyterian Life, 1965 October (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Community Facilities Plans
    - Community Facilities Plan And Public Improvement Program, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Manchester, New Hampshire, 1964 April (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Conference Directories
    - Conference On State Planning Administration, 1935 December (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - A Strategy for Planning: A Report To the National Governors' Conference, 1967 October (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Development and Campus Plans
    - Casebook on Campus Planning and Institutional Development, Undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Case Studies of Campus Plans, Undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Development Trends, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - The New Campus In Britain: Ideas Of Consequence for the United States, 1965 July (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - York College Master Plan 1975, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Long Range Development Plan
      - University of California, Davis, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 10)
      - University of California, Irvine, 1963 June (Box 21, Folder 11)
      - University of California, Los Angeles, 1963 December (Box 21, Folder 12)
      - University of California, Riverside, 1964 May (Box 21, Folder 13)
      - University of California, Santa Barbara, 1963 November (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Unity and Diversity: The Academic Plan Of The University Of California, 1965-1975 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Economics and Planning
    - Contrasts In Agglomeration: New York And Pittsburgh, 1961 May (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - The Fiscal Impact of Residential And Commercial Development: A Case Study, 1972 December (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Institute of Government And Republic Affairs, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Progress In Urban Economics, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Economic Area Analysis
    - California
      - Los Angeles: The Economic Outlook, 1946 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Studies in the Economy of Downtown San Francisco, 1963 September (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Colorado
      - Economic Growth In The Denver SMSA, 1965-1985, 1967 August (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - Working Denver, 1953 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Illinois
      - The Economic Potential Of the Davenport - Rock Island - Moline Metropolitan Area: A First Report (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Kentucky
      - Economic Survey, 1965 April (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Maryland
      - Maryland County Economic Data Book, 1964 April (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Massachusetts
      - Economic Base And Population Study, 1967 March (Box 22, Folder 12)
      - The Economic Base Study, 1964 September (Box 22, Folder 13)
      - Interim Forecasts Of Aggregate Population, Employment And Income, 1965-2000, 1965 September (Box 22, Folder 14)
      - Profile And Analysis Of Economic Data For Massachusetts, 1968 October (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Michigan
      - The Detroit Area Economic Fact Book, 1967 March-1968 March (Box 23, Folder 1-2)
      - The Kalamazoo County Economy, 1960 April (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - New England
      - Federal Reserve Bank Of Boston Annual Report: The New England Economy in 1970, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - New England: Dimensions For Growth, 1960-2000 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - New England Economic Almanac, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - New England Economic Indicators, 1969 September-1970 April (Box 23, Folder 7-10)
    - New Hampshire
      - Economic Changes In Each New Hampshire County, 1957 to 1965, 1965 May (Box 23, Folder 11)
      - New Hampshire Initial Town Property Survey Report, 1957, 1959 January (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - New Jersey
      - Bergen County Economic Indicators, 1968-1970 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - New York
      - Economic Characteristics Of The Syracuse Area, 1943 (Box 23, Folder 14)
      - Interindustry Studies And Model Development, 1969 February (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Ohio
      - An Economic Model Of Ohio, 1968 February (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Pennsylvania
      - An Economic Atlas Of Pennsylvania, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - Economic Characteristics, Undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - A Regional Economic Study Of Cameron County, 1967 December (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Rhode Island
      - Economic Inventory, 1964 July (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Rhode Island Basic Economic Statistics, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Economic Development
    - Accelerating Economic Growth In Arkansas, 1964 October (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Application of Activity Analysis to Regional Development Planning, 1965 March (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Arkansas' Strategy for Ozarks Development, 1967 August (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Attracting New Industry, Undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Bibliography Of Studies On the Economic Development Of Pennsylvania And Its Regions, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - The Community and Economic Development, 1964 May (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - The Community Goes Into Business, 1948 March (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - A Demonstration Economic Development Program For Harlem, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Development Program for the Ohio Valley Region, 1964-1965 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Economic Revitalization In The Confluence Region: An Argument For A Regional Scale Approach To Areas Of Depression, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Empirical Study Of Urban Growth In California, 1965 December (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - The Impact Of Federal Spending in California, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Investment Opportunities in South Central Alaska, 1965 March (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - The Michigan Economy: Prospects and Problems, 1962 June (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Multi-County Programming And Implementation For Economic Development, 1964 July (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Plain Talk On Economic Renewal In New York City, 1966 September (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Planning California's Future Development, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Regional Industrial Development Corporation Annual Report (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Strategies. Models, and Economic Theories Of Development In Rural Regions, 1967 December (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - A Suggested Program For Financing Area Development In Michigan, 1960 December (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Urban And Regional Imbalances In Economic Development (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Water Resources And Regional Economic Growth In The United States, 1950-1960, 1968 April (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Wisconsin's Economic Development, 1965 April (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Education and Educational Facilities
    - Alternative Measures Of Fiscal Redistribution: Gross vs. Net Aid, 1968 April (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - The Elementary And Secondary Education Act: A Distributional Analysis, 1968 April (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Measuring The Regional Impact Of Government Spending, 1968 May (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Historic Preservation and Rehabilitation
    - Annapolis Roundtable Conference, The Growth of Historic Towns, Undated (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Annual Report of the Historic Districts Commission, Town of Nantucket, Massachusetts, 1963-1965 (Box 25, Folder 19-20)
    - Architectural Preservation: Europe-French And English Contributions, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - The Boston Land Company, 1873 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - A Current View Of Area Preservation, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - A Graphic Guide To Decentralization, 1944 October (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Preservation Of Historic Sites, 1966 November (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Preserving Historic America, 1966 June (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Preserving Norfolk's Heritage, 1965 December (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Reconnaissance Report Waterfront Historic Area, New Bedford, Massachusetts, Undated (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Housing
    - Construction
      - Building Activity Survey, 1968 January-1968 December (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - Building Activity: Twenty Year Summary, 1966 August (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Cooperative
      - Co-op City, Undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - Co-op City Dedication, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - Co-op City Site Plan, Undated (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - Co-op City Times, 1970 Feb, April (Box 26, Folder 6-7)
      - The Cooperator, 1970 April (Box 26, Folder 8)
      - Social Aspects Of Cooperative And Non-Profit Housing, 1968 February (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Economics
      - The Cost Of Slums In Newark, 1946 (Box 26, Folder 10)
      - Financing Of Housing And Community Improvement Programs, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 11)
      - The Garden Apartment Development: A Municipal Cost-Revenue Analysis, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 12)
      - Home Finance And Housing Quality In Aging Neighborhoods, 1965 February (Box 26, Folder 13)
      - How To Finance Your Home, 1964 May (Box 26, Folder 14)
      - Intercity Comparisons Of Housing Costs (Box 26, Folder 15)
      - The Necessary Revolution In Housing Finance, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 16)
      - Nonbusiness Construction, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 17)
      - The Position Of Housing In National Economic And Social Policy, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 18)
      - Profile Of The Los Angeles Metropolis, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 19)
      - Residential Property In San Francisco: A Study Of Price Movements And Trends In Financing, 1960-1964, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 20)
      - Some Theory And Policy Implications Of The Postwar Housing Boom, 1966 May (Box 26, Folder 21)
      - A Theory Of Fluctuations In Residential Construction Starts, 1963 June (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Elderly
      - Community Aspects of Housing For The Aged (Box 26, Folder 23)
      - The Elderly And Their Housing (Box 26, Folder 24)
      - Federal Programs For Housing The Elderly, 1961 September (Box 26, Folder 25)
      - Housing For Senior Citizens: A Progress Report, 1964 April (Box 26, Folder 26)
      - Housing For The Elderly, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 27)
      - Housing For The Elderly; Annotated Reference, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 28)
      - Inventory Of Federally Financed Retirement Housing In California, Undated (Box 26, Folder 29)
      - Proceedings Of The Interfaith Conference On Housing For Senior Citizens, 1964 April (Box 26, Folder 30)
      - Resources For The Aging: An Action Handbook, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - 115, 000 Senior Citizens, Undated (Box 27, Folder 2)
      - Senior Citizens And How They Live: An Analysis Of 1960 Census Data, 1962 July (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Federal Housing Administration (FHA)
      - FHA Financing For Rental Housing, "A Hypothetical Case", 1966, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 4-6)
      - FHA Financing For Sales Housing: "A Hypothetical Case", 1969 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Federal National Mortgage Association (FNMA)
      - Background And History Of The Federal National Mortgage Association, 1938...1963, 1963 July (Box 27, Folder 8)
      - Information Regarding The Activities Of The Association, 1938 April (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Income
      - Low Income
        - Cooperation Of The Public And Private Sectors In Housing, 1968 April (Box 27, Folder 10)
        - Guide To Federal Low And Moderate Income Housing And Community Development Programs, 1968 December (Box 27, Folder 11)
        - People, Dwellings And Neighborhoods, 1978 March (Box 27, Folder 12)
        - Rent Subsidies, Recommended Guidelines, 1964 November (Box 27, Folder 13)
        - Rent Supplement Program, 1966 May (Box 27, Folder 14)
        - Ways And Means Of Providing Housing For Families Unable To Afford Rentals Or Mortgage Payments Necessary For Adequate Private Housing, 1960 December (Box 27, Folder 15)
      - Middle Income
        - Chicago Dwellings Association, Annual Report, 1966-1967 (Box 27, Folder 16-17)
        - New Opportunities For Open Occupancy...Through Nonprofit Sponsorship, 1968 January (Box 27, Folder 18)
        - Nonprofit Landlord, Undated (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Investment
      - Investment Performance, 1965 December (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - ' 20-20' Hindsight, Project Lending In Retrospect, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Markets
      - Analysis Of The Chicago Illinois Standard Metropolitan Statistical Area Housing Market, 1966 June (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Income Redistribution And The Urban Housing Market, 1968 September (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Locational Preferences In The Urban Housing Market, 1961 November (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Report On Home Buyers Preferences, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Statistical surveys for United States Housing Markets, 1967-1969 (Box 28, Folder 7-11)
    - Minority
      - The Comparative Cost Of Housing For White, Nonwhite And Puerto Rican Families In the New York Metropolitan Area, Undated (Box 28, Folder 12)
      - The Heart Of The Matter: More Housing For Negroes, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 13)
      - How The Federal Government Builds Ghettos, 1967 February (Box 28, Folder 14)
      - Minority Group Housing Problems, 1967 February (Box 28, Folder 15)
      - Planning For Open City, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 16)
      - Rent and Quality Of White And Negro Housing In Manhattan, New York, Undated (Box 28, Folder 17)
      - Toward Integration In Suburban Housing, Undated (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Minority Housing Legislation
      - Politics, Housing and Race Relations: The Defeat of Berkeley's Fair Housing Ordinance, 1965 November (Box 28, Folder 19)
      - A Report To The Mayor And The City Council Of Chicago On The Present Status And Effectiveness Of Existing Fair Housing Practices Legislation In The United States As Of August 31, 1697, 1967 August (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Mobile Homes
      - Minimum Property Standards for Mobile Home Courts, 1962 August (Box 28, Folder 21)
      - Select Data On Mobile Home/Trailer Regulations In Cities And Towns In Rhode Island Mobile Home Regulation In Rhode Island, Undated (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Mortgage Insurance
      - Effect Of Federal Mortgage Underwriting On Residential Construction, 1967 January (Box 28, Folder 23)
      - Investment Of Institutional Funds In FHA Insured Mortgages, 1967 March (Box 28, Folder 24)
      - Loan Closing Costs On Single-Family Homes In Six Metropolitan Areas, 1965 May (Box 28, Folder 25)
      - Regional Cycles Of Residential Housing Construction And The Interregional Mortgage Market: 1954-1959, 1963 February (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Programs
      - The City's Limited Profit Housing Program, 1968 May (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - Division Of Housing And Community Renewal, 1980 March (Box 29, Folder 2)
      - For Better Housing In Illinois, 1967 April (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - Housing As The Keystone: Proposed Housing Element For A Regional Planning Study Design, 1967 April (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - Housing, Better Homes For Better Communities, 1968 October (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - New York State Division Of Housing And Community Renewal Annual Report, 1980-1981 (Box 29, Folder 6)
      - Our Housing Dilemma, 1967 January (Box 29, Folder 7)
      - Project Data, 1974 December (Box 29, Folder 8)
      - The Pursuit of Housing Policy Goals In New York City, 1965 March (Box 29, Folder 9)
      - Statistical Summary Of Programs, 1985 March (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Public Housing Agencies
      - Apartment Development, 1965 May (Box 29, Folder 11)
      - The First Six Months, 1958 November (Box 29, Folder 12)
      - Apartments, Getting The Number, Size, Design And Location, 1965 November (Box 29, Folder 13)
      - The Housing Authority Of The City Of New Haven, Annual Report, 1968, 1984-1985 (Box 29, Folder 14-16)
      - New Neighborhoods, New Lives, 1964 September (Box 29, Folder 17)
      - Report On Family Living In High Rise Apartment Buildings, 1965 May (Box 29, Folder 18)
      - A Study Of Motel-Apartments, 1964 May (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Public Housing Management, Tenants and Tenant Services
      - Community Planning For Concerted Services in Public Housing, 1964 October (Box 29, Folder 20)
      - A Handbook Of Landlord-Tenant Procedures And Law With Forms, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 21)
      - Rent Rebates: A Guide To The Greater London Council Scheme, 1968 June (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Public Housing Projects
      - Methods Of Reducing The Cost Of Public Housing, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - Public Housing In Milwaukee, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Rehabilitation
      - Multifamily Rehabilitation, Information Guide and Instruction Handbook, Undated (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Statistics
      - Census Of Housing, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - Housing And Dwelling Units, 1960-1966, 1967 October (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - Housing Statistics Handbook, 1964 October (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - Rent And Quality Of White And Negro Housing In Manhattan, New York, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - Statistical Summary Of Programs, 1984 March (Box 30, Folder 8)
      - United States Census Of Housing: 1960, 1961 June (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Surveys
      - Housing And Population, Undated (Box 30, Folder 10)
      - Housing Quality Index, 1956 December (Box 30, Folder 11)